Well, we'll we'll we'll do the call of order and the pledge of allegiance.
So
I pledge allegiance
to the flag of The United States and we're gonna stand it. And to the republic for which it stands. For which it stands, one nation under God,
indivisible,
with liberty and justice for all. Before
>> we get started,
sad news that
I found out we all pretty much found out in the last couple of days. Scott Person's mother, Jeannie Person,
passed away,
longtime resident of Andover,
mother of eight children.
We need to recognize her. We'll probably recognize her as well at the next meeting.
So I do not believe that Scott will be joining us, so I just
let that be known.
Public speak.
Louise Goodwin, would you like to
speak to the board before our meeting?
No, just listening. Thank you. Item
>> three,
deletions to the agenda.
I'm going to make a motion that we delete item six, executive session, to discuss the building official position.
Will someone second that? I'll second that. All right.
Does anyone want to discuss that?
I don't believe we should.
We're moving forward in a direction I have another phone call scheduled with him for tomorrow.
New business. Discuss and act upon the following the contract ratification of the new public works supervisor position.
Eric, would you like to
>> Sure.
You
have all gotten a couple of drafts of the contract,
and you should have all had a copy of the final draft of copy that was signed by myself and Jay.
But it's not technically efficient or official until you as a board
ratify
the
make a resolution to approve the contract.
>> Okay.
Dennis before we vote on this do you have any issues and anything related to the contract that you'd like to bring up to us?
>> No, I think I sent over to Eric by email a draft resolution.
Do you have it Eric? I don't I don't Yes.
>> Okay. I sent that around to the board earlier today
or I could share my screen and I have it up on the share.
>> No. I I, you know, I I certainly had something to do with
finalizing this contract and I think it's very good.
It's based on some of the ones that we've done in the past, using using them as a template of course, but it's a little simpler of course than Eric's contract.
But,
I think it's very good and,
I think it's,
you know, something that you ought to approve if you see fit.
Okay. As far as as far as legally
goes.
>> Okay.
Does anyone have any questions on the
on the applicant
that we chose or why we chose them or anything?
I
would make a motion that we accept
the contract.
>> Well, where is that motion before Adrian goes too far? All right, I'm gonna pull it up here in two seconds. You
>> should be looking at it and it is the top motion.
Yeah.
Okay.
>> I hereby move
pursuant to town charter section seven zero one, seven zero two ms and seven zero two j that Robert J. Tuttle be appointed
by the Boris Lockman to serve the town of Andover as public works supervisor
and the tree warden in strict accordance and compliance to attached employee agreement between town of Andover
and Robert j Tuttle
The position description for the public works supervisor
as attached there too.
>> So moved this December 2020 by the board of selectmen.
I'll second that.
Further discussion on it?
No? All those in favor?
Aye.
I don't have Jeff on my screen. One second. Are we all good? Did Jeff do it? Oops, I got the wrong computer.
Okay, we're all good.
So that's passed.
Right. The other motion we will not deal with.
All right. Is there anything else that we need to deal with in this meeting?
No?
Public speak?
Louise,
would you like to give us any final?
No, just happy holidays.
>> Okay. Thank you. You as well. You as well. Thank you. Excellent. Am I missing anyone on
>> the meeting? I got to look.
Doesn't look like I am.
All right.
Okay, that's excellent. Since we're not going into executive session, would someone like to make a motion to adjourn?
I make a motion to adjourn.
I'll
second it.
All those in favor?
Aye. Aye.
>> Dennis, thank you for taking the time out of your evening to come join us. Well, it wasn't much time and it's always a pleasure.
All right. Thank you very much. I hope you enjoyed your Thanksgiving. Amanda, you are always the best. Thank you very much. Appreciate it. Eric, thank you. You guys, we'll be talking tomorrow.
So we'll be good. All right. All right. Thank you.